<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

  <ui:style src="../../style.css" />

	<g:HTMLPanel styleName="{style.panel}">
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Privacy Policy">Privacy Policy</ui:msg> </div>
<p class="{style.sectionItalic}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how LinguaeLive, LLC collects and uses the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using the LinguaeLive service located at www.LinguaeLive.ca (the Website).">This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how LinguaeLive, LLC collects and uses the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using the LinguaeLive service located at www.LinguaeLive.ca (the "Website").</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionItalic}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="By using or accessing the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.">By using or accessing the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Information We Collect">Information We Collect</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="When you visit the Website, you provide us with two types of information: (i) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and (ii) use information collected by us as you interact with the Website.">When you visit the Website, you provide us with two types of information: (i) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and (ii) use information collected by us as you interact with the Website.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="When you register with the Website, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your school, your course, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.">When you register with the Website, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your school, your course, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="When you enter the Website, the Website collects your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Website visitors. In addition, the Website stores certain information from your browser using cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. The Website uses session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, the Website uses a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to the Website. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.">When you enter the Website, the Website collects your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Website visitors. In addition, the Website stores certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. The Website uses session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, the Website uses a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to the Website. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="You post content in the form of text, files, images, photos, works of authorship, any other material or information that is uploaded to, posted to or otherwise communicated by users on the Website (collectively, “Content”) at your own risk. The Website cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your information. Therefore, the Website cannot and does not guarantee that Content you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. The Website is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your Content.">You post content in the form of text, files, images, photos, works of authorship, any other material or information that is uploaded to, posted to or otherwise communicated by users on the Website (collectively, “Content”) at your own risk. The Website cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your information. Therefore, the Website cannot and does not guarantee that Content you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. The Website is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your Content.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on the Website is a violation of LinguaeLive’s terms of service and should be reported to support&nbsp;@&nbsp;linguaelive.ca&nbsp;.">Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on the Website is a violation of LinguaeLive’s terms of service and should be reported to support&nbsp;@&nbsp;linguaelive.ca&nbsp;.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Use of Information Obtained by the Website">Use of Information Obtained by the Website</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We may use this information to">We may use this information to</ui:msg></p>
<ul> 
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Respond to users’ service requests;">Respond to users’ service requests;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Administer your account;">Administer your account;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Send you periodical email newsletters about new features and services, significant updates to the Website or marketing communications;">Send you periodical email newsletters about new features and services, significant updates to the Website or marketing communications;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Respond to your questions and concerns;">Respond to your questions and concerns;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Improve our Website and marketing efforts;">Improve our Website and marketing efforts;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Conduct research and analysis;">Conduct research and analysis;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Display content based upon your interests;">Display content based upon your interests;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Facilitate your transactions with other users; and">Facilitate your transactions with other users; and</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="List you in our searchable directories.">List you in our searchable directories.</ui:msg></li>
</ul>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Choice/Opt-Out">Choice/Opt-Out</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at optout&nbsp;@&nbsp;linguaelive.ca&nbsp;.">You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at optout&nbsp;@&nbsp;linguaelive.ca&nbsp;.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We enable you to create a profile, and share information with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.">We enable you to create a profile, and share information with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="When you register with the Website, you create your own account. Your username and email will be attached to material you upload on the Website.">When you register with the Website, you create your own account. Your username and email will be attached to material you upload on the Website.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Information Sharing">Information Sharing</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.  We do not sell, share, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for their promotional purposes.">We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.  We do not sell, share, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for their promotional purposes.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We may provide your personal information to third parties that provide services to help us with our business activities such as maintaining the Website and providing customer service. These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.">We may provide your personal information to third parties that provide services to help us with our business activities such as maintaining the Website and providing customer service. These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We may also disclose your personal information">We may also disclose your personal information</ui:msg></p>
<ul>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;">as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; and">when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; and</ui:msg></li>
<li><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.">to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.</ui:msg></li>
</ul>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We make your contact information available to other users that you transact with on this site to help facilitate your interaction and language learning.">We make your contact information available to other users that you transact with on this site to help facilitate your interaction and language learning.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Links">Links</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="The Website may contain links to other websites. The Website is of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. The Website encourages users to be aware when they leave the Website to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Website.">The Website may contain links to other websites. The Website is of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. The Website encourages users to be aware when they leave the Website to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Website.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Third Party Advertising">Third Party Advertising</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Advertisements that appear on the Website are sometimes delivered (or served) directly to users by third-party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. The Website does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on the Website unless you choose to share it with them.">Advertisements that appear on the Website are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third-party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. The Website does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on the Website unless you choose to share it with them.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by the Website and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.">This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by the Website and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Changing or Removing Information">Changing or Removing Information</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Users may modify or remove any of their account information at any time by logging into the My Profile page.  Information will be updated promptly. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Website account may do so on the My Profile page.">Users may modify or remove any of their account information at any time by logging into the My Profile page.  Information will be updated promptly. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Website account may do so on the My Profile page.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Protecting Information">Protecting Information</ui:msg></div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="The Website takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, the Website requests that you not send private information to us by email.">The Website takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, the Website requests that you not send private information to us by email.</ui:msg></p>
<div class="{style.sectionHeader}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Changes in this Privacy Statemen">Changes in this Privacy Statemen</ui:msg>t</div>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.">If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.</ui:msg></p>
<p class="{style.sectionDesc}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.">We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.</ui:msg></p>
<p />
<p class="{style.sectionItalic}"><ui:msg meaning="Privacy" description="Last Updated April 30, 2011.">Last Updated April 30, 2011.</ui:msg></p>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 